<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Datatable xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">

  <!-- lilyophelia: Endless Romance | Start -->
  <!-- lilyophelia: French localization: archlordluc; shavounet; Marlo -->
  <!-- lilyophelia: German localization: Ptah -->
  <!-- lilyophelia: Italian localization: Peshku -->
  <!-- lilyophelia: Russian localization: BadBecauseMad -->

  <!-- DO  NOT TRANSLATE; TEMPLATES -->
  <!-- Quest Template -->
  <!--
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Template_Title">Trade Fleet In Danger</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Template_Description">A foreign trade fleet is broadcasting a distress signal from the edge of one of your systems. They appear to be badly damaged and they are asking for assistance.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Template_OptionName_Title">Ignore</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Template_OptionName_Description">Ignore the distress call.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Template_OptionName_Objective">Your empire does not have time to deal with this situation. Besides, it might be a trap. Whoever these traders are, they're on their own. [End of Romance]</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Template_OptionName_ObjectiveTooltip">[End of Romance]</LocalizationPair>
  -->  

  <!-- TRANSLATE NOW -->   
  <!-- lilyophelia: normally located in ES2_Localization_Locales.xml -->
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%QuestTypeEndlessRomanceTitle">Endless Romance</LocalizationPair>  
  
  <!-- lilyophelia: normally located in ES2_Localization_Quest_Locales.xml -->
  
  <!-- Quest -->
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Introduction_Title">Endless Romance</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Introduction_Description">Endless Romance is a high-quality quest mod that adds a massive amount of new story and depth to your ES2 playthroughs.

------------------
Features 
------------------

Character Plot Webs: Adds deep, fleshed out (and romanceable) characters to your ES2 playthroughs. Released Dec 2017.

Adventures: Adds shorter quest lines that inject interesting events, mysteries, stories and dillemas into your ES2 games. Released Dec 2017.

History System: Adds a large assortment of buildable histories, based on your story choices during your playthrough of Endless Romance. Histories are like mini-wonder buildings that provide a thematic bonus (flat + scaling) and make your empire feel more personalized and storied. Adds more than 6 Illustrations. Released Jan 2018.

New Heroes: Recruit the characters you meet in stories to govern your worlds and guide your fleets. Released Jan 2018.

-----------------
Content
-----------------

Total Content: adds more than 1 Romanceable Hero, 34 New Events, 85 Unique Choices, 19 Different Endings, 3 Exciting Epilogues, 8 Buildable Histories, and 18 Original Illustrations. 

---

Aurelia: Meet a charming, golden-eyed trade princess and her people. Save--or exploit--her crew when they ask for help. Form a trade alliance, resettle them as refugees on your homeworld, or maybe just process them for food or dust. Take Aurelia on as an advisor or a lover. Visit an uninhabited, primal moon and forge a deep bond based on love, trust and mutual respect. 

New Character Plot Web, adding the new hero, "Aurelia the Lover," and more than 26 Events, 67 Choices, 11 Endings, 0 Histories, and 5 Illustrations. Released Dec 2017

---

Temporal Anomaly: Investigate strange flashes of light at the edge of one of your systems. Do your best to avoid a mysterious black hole. Investigate a derelict, ghost ship.

New Adventure, adding more than 2 Events, 5 Choices, 4 Endings, 1 Epilogue, 4 Histories, and 4 Illustrations. Released Dec 2017

---

The Warship: Hunt down a stealthy enemy shuttle. Capture prisoners and interrogate them for information. Uncover their secret mission and make an important diplomatic choice. Confiscate an advanced vessel of war. Endure a viral outbreak.

New Adventure, adding more than 5 Events, 13 Choices, 4 Endings, 2 Epilogues, 4 Histories and 3 Illustrations. Released Jan 2018

---------------------
Next Update
---------------------

Jan 30th @ 2PM PST

- Ziggurat of the Dark Goddess: Free an imprisoned, pagan Vodyani Goddess; a dark and psychic being. New character plot web.

----------------------
Coming Soon!
----------------------

New adventures, new histories and new heroes!

Future characters to include: Viktor (Nihilistic War General); a dark Vodyani goddess; a Riftborn developing emotions/personality; a pacifist, vegan Craver scientist who is always hungry; an Unfallen flapper-girl that loves sarcastic poetry

-----------------
Credits
-----------------

Story, writing and coding by lilyophelia (project lead/owner)
Story and artwork by IvyFetish
French localization by: archlordluc; shavounet; Marlo
German localization by Ptah; lasersword
Russian localization by BadBecauseMad (aka BBM); Bin

If you'd like to join one of our wonderful localization teams, please get in touch!</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Introduction_Activate_Title">Activate</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Introduction_Activate_Description">Start the Endless Romance Mod.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Introduction_Activate_Objective">Load the Endless Romance Mod for this playthrough.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Introduction_Activate_ObjectiveTooltip">New characters and events will periodically appear during your game.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Introduction_Disable_Title">Disable</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Introduction_Disable_Description">Disable the Endless Romance Mod.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Introduction_Disable_Objective">Disable the Endless Romance Mod for this playthrough.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Introduction_Disable_ObjectiveTooltip">There will be no changes to your game for this playthrough.</LocalizationPair>

 <!-- Quest -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Warning_Title">Warning! Endless Romance Not Loaded</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Warning_Description">You need to manually select the Activate option below if you would like to load Endless Romance for this playthrough.

We create this content for players only. This is the only way we can prevent the AI Empires from going on your adventures and romancing your characters!

Sorry for the inconvenience! Please make sure to select Activate below.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Warning_Activate_Title">Activate</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Warning_Activate_Description">Start the Endless Romance Mod.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Warning_Activate_Objective">Load the Endless Romance Mod for this playthrough.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Warning_Activate_ObjectiveTooltip">New characters and events will periodically appear during your game.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Warning_Disable_Title">Disable</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Warning_Disable_Description">Disable the Endless Romance Mod.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Warning_Disable_Objective">Disable the Endless Romance Mod for this playthrough.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EndlessRomance_Warning_Disable_ObjectiveTooltip">There will be no changes to your game for this playthrough.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- lilyophelia: Endless Romance | End -->

</Datatable>